

	Kenmore, WA 98028
	https://claythedreamer.netlify.app
$\bowtie$	clay1013@gmail.com
in	www.linkedin.com/in/claythedreamer



I recently graduated with a degree in Information Technology from Lake Washington Institute of Technology. I'm passionate about web and app development, especially when it comes to UX/UI and interactive design. I love creating software that's not just functional, but also easy to use and nice to look at. My focus is always on making sure the user has a great experience with the software I build.

X	SKILLS							
		HTML, JS, CSS		jQuery / JSON		Java		React JS
		C#		Photoshop / Illustrator		Agile/Scrum		Figma

## **EDUCATION**

BAS, Information Technology | Lake Washington Institute of Technology

2020 - 2024

Computing and Software Development

AAS, Computing & Software Development | Lake Washington Institute of Technology

2020 - 2022

C++/C# Web Developer Certification

BA, Art/Art Studies | University of Washington

2010 - 2013

## WORK EXPERIENCE

**Contract Specialist | Peraclete Technologies** 

2021 - PRESENT

Control data privacy and security by utilizing specialized software tools.

**Aircraft Technician | The Boeing Company** 

2021 - PRESENT

Read and comprehend technical work instructions. Clean, seal, close, and test integral fuel tanks on aircraft.

## PROJECTS

**Bible Tracker | Capstone Project |** https://github.com/clay-kim/BibleTracker
Built a web app for tracking Bible verse reading progress. Features user authentication, data visualization, and AWS integration. Built with RDS(MySQL), Lambda, API Gateway, React.js, CSS, JavaScript.

**Artist portfolio website | React JS |** https://gc-clay-art.netlify.app

Created a fully responsive website for viewing and selling art. Employed React.js for a dynamic UI and ensured cross-device compatibility. Built with React.js, CSS, HTML, JavaScript.